springleaffinancial.com 2016-03-22

# Privacy Policy | Legal | Springleaf Financial Services

We understand your privacy is important. This website privacy policy describes our practices regarding information received about you during visits to the Site and supplements our Privacy Notice. 

"Site" means and includes any and all websites maintained by any of the Springleaf Financial Services family of companies, which includes Springleaf Finance, Inc. and all its subsidiaries and affiliates. The terms "we," "us," "our," or "Site Sponsor," as used on this Site, mean and include any all of the Springleaf Financial Services family of companies. 

**What types of information does Site Sponsor collect on this Site?**

Site Sponsor’s employees, representatives, agents and selected third parties may collect information about our customers and other visitors to this Site, including, but not limited to, aggregate information concerning: 

  * E-mail address and content
  * Domain name and IP address (e.g., aol.com) used to access the Internet
  * Internet address from which the visitor linked to the Site (e.g., www.yahoo.com)
  * Type of web browsing software used to view the Site
  * Date, time, and length of visit to the Site

 **What about Cookies and Web Beacons?** Cookies are small files containing alphanumeric characters that are used to identify your computer’s browser. Site Sponsor may send one or more Cookies to your computer to monitor your experience on the Site, and to allow us to improve the Site to better serve our customers and other users. Cookies may also be used to improve the security of the Site. No personally identifiable information about you, such as your name or social security number, is embedded in these Cookies. 

A Web Beacon is an electronic image (1x1 .gif) located within a certain web page. In some cases, Site Sponsor may use a Web Beacon to analyze traffic and transactions on this Site. No personally identifiable information about you, such as your name or social security number, is collected by any Site Sponsor Web Beacon. 

In cases where you may enter the Site from a third party site, such as a search engine or referral site, those sites may use Cookies and/or Web Beacons to monitor their own performance, traffic, etc. You must consult the privacy policy of each site, particularly at any sites provided by third parties, in order to determine what information about you is collected and how that information is used. 

Third party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on the internet. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads on a user’s prior visits to our Site. You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. 

Your browser should allow you to manage Cookies, and it may allow you to manage Web Beacons, used by various websites. However, if your browser’s settings are too restrictive you may not be able to use all of the features of a website, including this Site. 

**Can I confirm that the information Site Sponsor collects is correct?**

  * Keeping your account information accurate and up to date is very important. If you ever have questions or issues with the accuracy of your nonpublic personal information, please contact us at the following phone number or write us at the following address:
 **1-800-453-2017, Springleaf Finance, P.O. Box 3662, Evansville, IN 47735-3662.** We will promptly investigate your concerns and update our records as needed. 
  * We request that you keep your information as up to date as possible so that you may get the maximum benefit from Site Sponsor. In particular, please make sure that you inform us of e-mail address changes since this is the most rapid way to communicate.

 **How is information collected on this Site protected?**

  * Site Sponsor uses multiple levels of security regardless of the delivery channel you choose. We maintain personally identifying information in secure computer systems and we limit employee access to those with a business reason to see it. More specifically, employees may access information about you when needed to maintain your accounts or otherwise meet your needs. We safeguard information according to established security standards and procedures. Our employees are trained to understand and comply with these information principles. 
  * Site Sponsor is protected by a system of filtering routers and firewalls, which form a barrier between the outside Internet and the internal network. The filtering router verifies the source and destination of each network packet, and determines whether or not to let the packet through. Access is denied if the packet is not directed at a specific, available service. 

The firewall is used to shield Site Sponsor’s client service network from the Internet. All incoming IP traffic is actually addressed to the firewall, which is designed to allow only e-mail into the client service environment. Traffic through the firewall is subjected to a special proxy process which operates in much the same way as a filtering router, verifying the source and destination of each information packet. 

The proxy then changes the IP address of the packet to deliver it to the appropriate site within the client service network. In this way, all inside addresses are protected from outside access, and the structure of Site Sponsor’s internal networks is invisible to outside observers. 

**Am I protected when linking to other sites?**

  * This Site may, from time to time, contain links to other Internet websites, banner ads or advertisements for the convenience of users in locating information and services that may be of interest. If you use those linked Internet websites or advertisements, you may leave this Site and go to websites that we do not control. If you decide to visit those Internet sites or advertisers, you do so at your own risk and it is your responsibility to read and comply with the privacy statement on those websites. Your right to privacy on linked sites is limited to whatever rights are provided to you by the owner of the linked site. 
  * This Website Privacy Policy is for customers and visitors, and only applies to this Site. This Site only includes its home page and pages hereunder operated by Site Sponsor. This Website Privacy Policy does not apply to any linked site or any site provided by a third party. You must consult the privacy policy of such sites, in order to determine what information about you is collected and how that information is used. 

**Online Tracking**

  * Site Sponsor does not track its customers over time and across third party websites in order to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. However, some third party sites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve your content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you. If you are visiting such sites, most popular browsers (Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome, etc.) allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked. You should consult each site’s privacy policy to determine how that site’s operator responds to DNT signals 
  * Third parties that have content embedded on Site Sponsor's websites may set cookies on a user's browser and/or obtain information about the fact that a web browser visited a specific Site Sponsor website from a certain IP address. Third parties cannot collect any other personally identifiable information from Site Sponsor's websites unless you provide it to them directly. 

**Do We Collect Information about Children?**

  * We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from our Site about children under the age 13. We request that persons under the age of 18 not use our Site without supervision from a responsible adult. If a child whom we know to be under the age of 13 sends personal information to us online, we will only use that information to respond directly to that child, notify parents, or seek parental consent. 

**What About Transfer of Information to the United States?**

  * Our Site is operated in the United States and intended for users located in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including personal information, will be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your personal information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States. By using the Site or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing and storage of your information, including personal information, in the United States as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

**What About Changes to the Privacy Policy?**

  * We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy and your use of our Site indicates your consent to the privacy policy posted at the time of use. However, we will not use your previously collected personal information in a manner materially different than represented at the time it was collected without your consent. To the extent any provision of this Privacy Policy is found by a competent tribunal to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed to the extent necessary for the remainder to be valid and enforceable. 

**Additional Notices In Connection with the Springleaf Rewards Program**

  * Beginning on **[May 6th, 2015]** , Site Sponsor began offering the Springleaf Rewards Program (the "Program"), which is currently operated by a third party service provider on Site Sponsor’s behalf. Please be aware that when you enter the Program, you are leaving our Site and visiting a website that is operated by our service provider, CrowdTwist. However, this Privacy Policy will continue to apply to your use of the Program. Thus, when we use the terms "we," "us", or "our" in this Section, these terms shall be deemed to include both Site Sponsor and CrowdTwist. In addition to the provisions set forth in the Privacy Policy above, these additional notices apply to your participation in the Program, including any online service location (e.g., website or mobile app) you access when participating in the Program that posts or links to this Privacy Policy. These provisions also apply to all features, widgets, plug-ins, content, downloads and other features offered through the Program, regardless of how you access or use the Program, whether via computer, mobile device or otherwise: 

To the extent we provide you notice through the Program of different or additional privacy policies or practices (e.g., at the point of our collection), those additional terms shall govern such data collection and use. 

In addition, please review the Programs Terms of Service , which governs your participation and use of the Program. _By using our Program, you consent to our Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service and our collection, use and sharing of your information and data, and other activities, as described below._

  *  **Information You Provide to Us** In connection with the Program, we may ask you to provide us and/or our third party service providers with certain categories of information, such as: (1) personally identifiable information, which is information that identifies you personally, such as your first and last name and email address ("Personal Information"); and (2) demographic information, such as information about your gender or age ("Demographic Information"). We may collect this information through various forms and in various places in the Program, including if you sign-up for our Program’s online account management function as required in order to enter the Program or when you otherwise interact with the Program. If we combine Demographic Information with the Personal Information we collect directly from you in connection with the Program, we will treat the combined data as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. 
  * **Information Collected and Stored As You Access and Use the Program** In addition to any Personal Information (or other information that you choose to submit to us when using the Program), we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) store or collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the Program ("Usage Information"). This Usage Information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies that may be downloaded to your personal computer, browser, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other device (a "Device") whenever you visit or interact with our Program. This Usage Information may include: 
    * your IP address, UDID or other unique identifier ("Device Identifier"). A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device used to access the Program, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier;
    * your Device functionality (including browser, operating system, hardware, mobile network information);
    * the areas within our Program that you visit and your activities there, including remembering you, the frequency and duration of your use, and your preferences;
    * your Device location;
    * your Device characteristics; and
    * certain other Device data, including the time of day, and the address of the website from which you entered the Program, among other information.

We may use various methods and technologies to store or collect Usage Information such as Cookies and Web Beacons (as described above) (collectively, "Tracking Technologies"). There may be other Tracking Technologies now and later devised that are used by us in connection with the Program. We may use Tracking Technologies for a variety of purposes, including: 

    * **Strictly Necessary.** We may use Tracking Technologies that we consider are strictly necessary to allow you to use and access our Program, including cookies required to prevent fraudulent activity, improve security or allow you to make use of point redemption functionality. 
    * **Performance Related.** We may use Tracking Technologies that are useful in order to assess the performance of the Program, including as part of our analytic practices or otherwise to improve the activities, content, products or services offered through the Program. 
    * **Functionality Related.** We may use Tracking Technologies that are required to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing the Program, including identifying you when you use our Program or keeping track of your specified preferences, including in terms of the presentation of content on our Program. 
    * **Targeting Related.** We may use Tracking Technologies to deliver content relevant to your interests in our Program and third party services based on how you interact with our content. This includes using Tracking Technologies to understand the usefulness to you of the content that has been delivered to you. 
  * **Interactions with Third-Party Services** The Program may include functionality that allows certain kinds of interactions between the Program and a third-party web site or application. The use of this functionality may involve the third-party operator providing certain information, including Personal Information, to us. For example, after you sign-up for our online account management function as required in order to enter the Program, you may have an option to link your Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Foursquare or other account provided by a third-party site, platform or application to your Program account so that you may participate in certain types of Program point earning activities that we may offer from time to time. If we offer and you choose to use this account connecting functionality, the third-party site, platform or application may send Personal Information about you to us. If so, we will then treat it as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy, since we are collecting it as a result of your accessing of and interaction on our Program. In addition, we may provide third-party sites’ interfaces or links on the Program to facilitate your sending a communication from the Program. For example, we may use third parties to facilitate emails, posts, check-ins, Tweets or Facebook postings. These third parties may retain any information used or provided in any such communications or other activities and these third parties’ practices are not subject to our Privacy Policy. We may not control or have access to your communications through these third parties. Further, when you use third-party sites or services, you are using their services and not our services and they, not we, are responsible for their practices. You should review the applicable third-party privacy policies before using such third-party tools on our Program. 
  * **Information You Provide About a Third Party** You may send someone else a communication from the Program, such as sending an invitation to a friend. If so, the information you provide (names, email addresses, etc.) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used by us for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on our Program, your contact information, name or user name and message may be included in the communication sent to your addressee(s). Some of these tools may be third-party tools subject to third-party privacy policies. 
  * **How Do We Use the Information Collected in Connection with the Program?**

We may use your Personal Information, Demographic Information or Usage Information that is collected in connection with the Program: 

    * to process transactions or provide you with information such as to send you electronic newsletters or to provide you with special offers or promotional and marketing materials on behalf of us or third parties, including to let you know about new products, services or upcoming events; 
    * to enable you to participate in a variety of the Program’s features such as to enable you to participate in online entry sweepstakes, contests or other point earning activities or promotions and to award points for your completed Program activities; 
    * to process your joining the Program, including verifying your information is active and valid; 
    * to improve the Program, marketing endeavors or our Program offerings; 
    * to customize your experience in the Program or to serve you specific content or ads that are relevant to you; 
    * to fulfill rewards you earned through the Program; 
    * to provide customer support; 
    * to help diagnose problems with the Program; 
    * to contact you with regard to your use of the Program and, in our discretion, changes to the Program and/or Program’s policies or terms and conditions, including, but not limited to, the Terms of Service; 
    * to identify your product and Program preferences so that you can be informed of new or additional point earning activities, services and promotions; 
    * to improve the overall experience with the Program; 
    * for internal business purposes; and 
    * for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy or our a href="/legal/privacy-notice" 'Privacy Notice. 
  * **When do we Share Information with Third Parties?** A description of the types of parties with which we share your Personal Information, including, without limitation, in connection with the Program, is described specifically in our Privacy Notice. Also, please be aware that we share non-Personal Information, such as aggregated user statistics, with third parties. We may share your Device Identifiers with third parties along with data related to you and your activities. We also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Site or Program or applicable database; or (ii) in connection with a merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our interests and/or assets or other corporate change, including, during the course of any due diligence process. In addition, we may share the information we have collected about you, including Personal Information, as disclosed at the time you provide your information and as described below or otherwise in this Privacy Policy or in our Privacy Notice. 
  * **What About Information I Disclose Publicly or to Others?**
    *  **User Content** and Public Information. The Program may permit you to submit ideas, photographs, user profiles, writings, music, video, audio recordings, computer graphics, pictures, data, questions, comments, suggestions or other content, including Personal Information (collectively, " **User Content** "). We or others may store, display, reproduce, publish, distribute or otherwise use User Content online or offline in any media or format (currently existing or hereafter developed) and may or may not attribute it to you. Others may have access to this User Content and may have the ability to share it with third parties. Please think carefully before deciding what information you share, including Personal Information, in connection with your User Content. Please note that we do not control who will have access to the information that you choose to make public, and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy or keep it secure. We are not responsible for the privacy or security of any information that you make publicly available in the Program or what others do with information you share with them in the Program. We are not responsible for the accuracy, use or misuse of any User Content that you disclose or receive from third parties through the Program. 
    * **Name and Likeness.** We may also publish your name, voice, likeness and other Personal Information that is part of your User Content, and we may use the content, or any portion of the content, for advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities. For full terms and conditions regarding User Content you submit to the Program, please review our Terms of Service.
  *  **How Do I Change My Information and Communications Preferences?** You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information provided as part of signing up for our Program’s online account management function. The Program may allow you to review, correct or update Personal Information you have provided through the online account management function or the Program or otherwise, and you may provide informational updates and changes either through the Program’s online account management function or by contacting us via phone at (800) 325-2146. If so, we will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable (but we may retain prior information as business records). Please note that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons. Also, if you have made any public postings in the Program, such as in forums or blogs, these communications cannot generally be removed. When you edit your Personal Information or change your preferences in the Program, information that you remove may persist internally for our administrative purposes. You may modify our e-mail marketing communications that you receive from us about the Program by following the instructions contained within such e-mails. Such changes will only impact our e-mail communications to the extent described in the modification process. Any such modifications you request will not affect subsequent email subscriptions you may initiate in connection with the Program. If you subscribe to text messages from us in connection with the Program, you can terminate a particular text message subscription by reply texting "STOP." Subsequent or different text message subscriptions will be unaffected. Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Program such as administrative and service announcements and these transactional messages may be unaffected if you choose to opt-out from receiving our marketing communications regarding the Program. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy or practices described in it, you should contact us in the following ways: Phone Number: (800) 325-2146. 

**Additional Notices In Connection with Springleaf Perks** One feature integrated into the Program is Springleaf Rewards Perks ("Perks"). Perks is currently operated by a third party, Next Jump, Inc. ("Next Jump"). Please be aware that when you enter Perks, you are leaving our Site and visiting a website that is owned and operated by Next Jump. When you participate or visit the Perks site, Next Jump may collect Personal Information and other data from you and it has its own policies and practices that apply to the Perks site. We are not responsible for how Next Jump collects or uses your information and they may be tracking you across multiple sites and may be sharing the results of that tracking with us and/or others. Next Jump has its own terms of service, privacy policy and or other policies, and Next Jump may ask you to agree to the same. We are not responsible for the Next Jump policies or the practices of Next Jump. Be sure to review any available policies before submitting any Personal Information to a third-party or otherwise interacting with it and exercise caution in connection with your use of the Perks site. We also encourage you to note when you leave our Site and to review the third-party privacy policies of all third-party locations and exercise caution in connection with them. 

**Last Updated: May 2015**

 **This Site Privacy Policy is provided to you for informational purposes only. You do not need to call or take any action in response to this notice. We recommend that you read and retain this notice for your personal files.**

 **This Site Privacy Policy is provided to you for informational purposes only. You do not need to call or take any action in response to this notice. We recommend that you read and retain this notice for your personal files. Copyright 2015. Springleaf Finance, Inc. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved worldwide.**
